<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Thiago Vacare</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Thiago Vacare</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 20:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>97 Things Every Programmer Should Know - Kevlin Henney (Editor) ⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️</title><link>/books/book1/test/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/books/book1/test/</guid><description>I really like books with these small tips for your daily basis work, you start using it without even realising, which is great and this book is one of these.
&amp;ldquo;97 Things Every Programmer Should Know&amp;rdquo; is a book that each single &amp;ldquo;Thing&amp;rdquo; is written by a different author, and these authors are some very well known developers in the industry.
These are my favourites notes from this book:
Technical debt is like a loan: you benefit from it in the short term, but you have to pay interest on it until it is fully paid.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>/about/info/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2019 20:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/info/</guid><description>I’m Thiago Vacare, Software Engineer, I&amp;rsquo;ve been working mostly with Golang and Node.js in the last few years. I’m passionated about technology with a particular interest in the human side of software development. Studying code isn’t enough, you have to study the people behind the software, too. I also have interest in coding practices, system architecture and infrastructure. I decided to create this blog to write about technologies and I needed a way to write about new things whatever I discover or I’m working on.</description></item><item><title>Round Robin DNS with Docker</title><link>/round-robin-dns-with-docker/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/round-robin-dns-with-docker/</guid><description>For starters, we need to know what is round-robin DNS and how it works:
Round-robin load balancing is one of the simplest methods for distributing client requests across a group of servers. Going down the list of servers in the group, the round-robin load balancer forwards a client request to each server in turn. When it eaches the end of the list, the load balancer loops back and goes down the list again sends the next request to the first listed server, the one after that to the second server, and so on).</description></item></channel></rss>